Products

#### Get Started

[ClassOS

Engaging and interactive lessons](https://www.knowledgehook.com/teachers.html)[ClassOS Pro

Advanced classroom features](https://www.knowledgehook.com/classroom-pro.html)[After School

Home learning support for Parents](https://www.knowledgehook.com/parent-notactive.html)[Knowledgehook for Districts

District-wide classroom features](https://www.knowledgehook.com/administrators.html)

Solutions

#### Knowledgehook for

[Classrooms

Class-wide activities](https://www.knowledgehook.com/teachers.html)[Schools

Advanced classroom features](https://www.knowledgehook.com/classroom-pro.html)[Home

Home learning support for Parents](https://www.knowledgehook.com/parent-notactive.html)[School Districts

District-wide classroom features](https://www.knowledgehook.com/administrators.html)

Resources

[Log in](https://app.knowledgehook.com/app/login)[Log in](https://app.knowledgehook.com/app/login)[Student Log in

](http://www.joinkh.com/) [Student Login](http://www.joinkh.com/)[Sign up](https://app.knowledgehook.com/app/Register)

Privacy Policy  

=================

### Who We Are

Our mission at Knowledgehook is to help engage students with math practice and offer support to teachers and parents/guardians to improve their student or child’s mastery of math.  
‍  
Knowledgehook feels strongly about protecting your privacy. We understand how important privacy is to you and we are committed to creating a safe and secure environment for learners through our website, applications, and other means of interacting with us (collectively, our “Services”).

#### Table of Contents

### Our Privacy Principles

Our Privacy Notice is fuelled by our commitment to the following Privacy Principles:  
\- We’re deeply committed to creating a safe and secure online environment for you.  
\- We DO NOT sell your personal information to third parties. We take the protection of your information very seriously.  
\- We do not advertise on Knowledgehook. We use your information to provide you with a better learning experience.

### Consenting to Our Collection and Use of Your Information

Our Privacy Notice describes what information we gather from our members and others who visit and use our Services, how we use that information, and what we do to protect it. We require teachers to obtain parental consent via a consent form as part of the registration process. By visiting or using our Services, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this Privacy Notice.  
  
Your use of the Services and any information you provide on the Services are subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice, which is incorporated into and subject to our Terms of Service. Any capitalized terms used but not defined within this Privacy Notice have the meaning given to them in our Terms of Service.

### The Information We Collect from Our Users

At Knowledgehook, we take the information you provide to us very seriously and we strive to put you in control of decisions around your information.  
  
We collect limited personal information from students, teachers, parents/guardians, school-level administrators, and board-level administrators. We limit the information we collect from students to the minimal amount needed to use our service; often, a first name and last initial. We do not ask for information, such as gender, e-mail, address, or student ID. While students may be of any age, we, at Knowledgehook, provide all students with the same level of care as the legal protections for children age 13 or younger.  
  
Visit [here](https://www.knowledgehook.com/information-we-collect-from-our-users.html) to learn about what type of information we collect.

### Why We Collect Data

You signed up to use Knowledgehook’s service or because an authorized educational institution (a school or school district) shared information about you with Knowledgehook.  
  
In addition, we collect data for one of the following reasons:  
  
\- To enhance the Services we provide  
\- To understand how you and other Users use our Services  
\- To enable your participation in Knowledgehook partnership agreements  
  
**Knowledgehook Collects the Following Information About You and Your Use of Our Services:  
**  
**Personal Information.  
**When you register for, browse and use the Services, you may provide to Knowledgehook what is generally called “personally identifiable information” or “personal data” (such as your full name and email address) that can be used to identify you. At Knowledgehook, we call this data “Personal Information.”  
  
Visit [here](https://www.knowledgehook.com/information-we-collect-from-our-users.html) to learn about what type of information we collect.  
  
**Information about your use of our Services and other User-provided Information.  
**We may collect information about your use of certain Service features, such as the number of problems you have attempted, the number of videos you have viewed, and the amount of time spent to complete a problem. This enables us to better tailor educational experiences that are most appropriate for you.  
  
**Information obtained from other Users.  
**We may make available certain features that allow other Users to provide us information. This information may include Personal Information. For example, a teacher may register an account for their student and provide us with certain information, such as the student’s first name and last initial.  
  
**Google Classroom Integration.  
**A teacher may use [Google Classroom](https://classroom.google.com/) to import their student roster. In this scenario, we only access the class name and student names from Google Classroom. For stronger privacy, we store only the students' first name and last initial in our system instead of the full name, as well as Google ID (to allow Google Single Sign-On). We do not retrieve student e-mail addresses through Google Classroom.  
  
**Technical Information.**  
To provide a personalized learning and high-quality experience for our Users, we may use various technologies that automatically record certain technical information from your browser or device, including standard log files, web beacons, or pixel tags. This technical information may include your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring or exit pages, click stream data, operating system, and the dates and times that you use our Services and assists us in understanding how our Users are using our Services.  
  
**Cookies**.  
Like most websites, whether or not you are a registered member, we may send one or more cookies – small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters – to your computer. Cookies remember information about your activities on a website and enable us to provide you with a more personalized learning experience. Knowledgehook may use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears automatically after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to our Services. You can, however, remove a persistent cookie at any time. Please review your web browser “Help” file to learn the proper way to modify your cookie settings. However, without cookies you will not have access to certain services and features of our Services. We do not use cookies to collect any Personal Information, for behavioural advertising or to build a student profile unrelated to the use of Knowledgehook.  
  
**Third-Party Providers.  
**Knowledgehook may use a variety of third-party service providers, such as Vimeo to host our videos or Google Analytics and New Relic to understand our Service usage. We may allow third-party service providers to place and read their own cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect information through the Services. This information is collected directly and automatically by these third parties, and Knowledgehook does not participate in these data transmissions. Knowledgehook will, wherever feasible, contractually obligate our third-party service providers to abide by the terms of this Privacy Notice. We DO NOT sell or rent your Personal Information that we collect to third parties.  
  
**Information from Other Sources.  
**In certain situations, we may obtain information, including Personal Information, from third parties or sources other than our Services, such as when a teacher provides us with class lists or retrieves it from Google Classroom. If we combine or associate information from other sources with Personal Information that we collect through the Services, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Notice.  
  
**Knowledgehook Uses This Information In The Following Ways:  
****  
To enhance the Services we provide.  
**Knowledgehook uses the information you provide or that we collect to enhance our relationship with you and to operate, maintain, enhance, and improve our Services. Knowledgehook may, for instance, remember your recent activity so we can recommend the most appropriate content for you on your next visit. If you have given Knowledgehook consent, we may use your Personal Information to provide you with information about Knowledgehook’s features, services and other offerings that may be of interest to you.  
  
**To understand how you and other Users use our Services.  
**Knowledgehook uses all of the information that you provide or that we collect from Users to understand and analyze the usage trends, learning behaviors, and preferences of our Users, to improve the way our Services work and look, and to create new features and functionality.  
‍  
**To enable your participation in Knowledgehook partnership arrangements.  
**Knowledgehook will not share Personal Information with other third-party organizations for their marketing or promotional use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in. You may ask or authorize us to share your Personal Information with authorized partners, not-for-profit organizations, and other entities that are not affiliated with Knowledgehook. In these cases, we will provide to these third parties only the information you have authorized or asked us to share. Knowledgehook may send information or offers to you on behalf of these third parties. For example, we may partner with an organization running a contest in your region and send you an email notifying you of the partnership; if you opt-in to the program and indicate your approval, we may share your information with the third party to facilitate your participation in the program and enable you to redeem your prize.

### How We Share or Transfer Your Data

Knowledgehook takes great care to protect the information you provide us. We DO NOT rent or sell Personal Information that we collect from Users with third parties.  
  
**Knowledgehook Will Disclose User Information Only as Described Below:  
**  
**If you want information shared with other Users, we’ll share it for you.  
**Knowledgehook does not allow student-to-student communication. Students can upload their work and receive feedback from their teacher. Only your first name and last initial are shown here.  
  
**We may share anonymous or aggregate data to improve our services and learn more about our Users.  
**On certain occasions, Knowledgehook may work with business partners to improve our services or offerings. We may disclose automatically collected and other aggregate non-Personal Information to authorized business partners to conduct research on online education or assist in understanding the usage, viewing, and demographic patterns for certain programs, content, services, promotions, and/or functionality of the Services.  
  
**We will share data when required by law.  
**Knowledgehook may also disclose User information if required to do so by law, or if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with local, state, federal, international, or other applicable laws (such as Canadian Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant, or administrative request. In some cases, we may make such disclosures without first providing notice to Users.  
  
**We may share data in the context of a change of business, including a merger or acquisition.  
**In the event that Knowledgehook is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we may transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.  
  
**We may share data when necessary or appropriate to protect Knowledgehook or others.  
**Knowledgehook may disclose information that we believe, in good faith, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability; to protect Knowledgehook from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Services; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Knowledgehook, our Users, or others.

### How We Maintain Data Integrity

We don't own anything you add to Knowledgehook, you do. At Knowledgehook, we only use Personal Information as needed for the purposes for which it was collected or where you have consented to our use of Personal Information relating to you. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the Personal Information we store and use is accurate, complete, and up-to-date. At any time, you can request to learn about what data we have related to you, how we collected this data, how we use it, how you can modify inaccurate data, and how you can remove it. If you discover that Personal Information or other data pertaining to you is inaccurate, incomplete, or out-of-date, please update your account information or contact our support team (see “Contacting Knowledgehook” here).

### Our Approach to Data Security

**Security and Privacy is important to you and to us.  
**To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections to your information. We may ask you to provide certain Personal Information to confirm your identity, and may require that you create and use a password to access certain parts of our Services. You should create and maintain a strong password to help ensure the security of your account.  
  
**We try to ensure that our Services and information sent to us are safe, but no security measures are perfect.  
**Knowledgehook uses certain physical, managerial, and technical safeguards designed to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information and other information we maintain in connection with the Services. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any or all of the information you transmit to Knowledgehook, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Knowledgehook makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards.  
  
We will notify you electronically or via the Services if Knowledgehook experiences a data security incident that could affect you, immediately, and once the incident has been resolved.  
  
If we learn of a data security incident that compromises or appears to compromise your Personal Information, then we will attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. We may also post a notice on our website if a data security incident occurs.  
  
**We take great security measures to protect your information.  
**Knowledgehook takes great measures to ensure that we uphold our commitment to protecting your privacy and the data we have related to you. All data is stored in a way that is not publicly accessible, and we only use and collect your information as stated in this Privacy Notice.  
  
Our servers are in highly secure data centers that are access-controlled. We host our application using best-in-class security measures to prevent unauthorized access. They are safeguarded with tools like Threat Intelligence, Advanced Threat Analytics, Information Protection, SSL Encryption, and Multi-Factor Authorization.  
  
**We limit access to your Personal Information by employees and authorized parties.  
**Knowledgehook’s employees, agents and contractors must have a legitimate business reason to access Personal Information you provide to Knowledgehook. We may share your Personal Information with third-party service providers, including outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities, but they may only use your Personal Information to provide us with a specific service and not for any other purpose. Where feasible, Knowledgehook will require our third-party service providers to comply with this Privacy Notice.  
  
**We ensure limited access to students’ Personal Information.  
**Only the students themselves and their connected parent, teacher or school leader can see a student's portfolio and math results. Game information unrelated to math achievement, such as avatars collected, may be visible to other users on the platform.

### How and When This Privacy Policy Can Change

We update and review our Privacy Policy at least once a year and whenever there is a substantial change in the law or our policy and procedure. We want to continually improve the Knowledgehook experience for you and so our terms may change from time to time. We will do everything we reasonably can to update you about these changes ahead of time. We will notify you of any significant changes to our policy. Before continuing to use Knowledgehook, it will be important to re-review and agree to any changes.  
  
See how we comply with legal frameworks [here](https://staticcontent.knowledgehook.com/content/documents/privacy/knowledgehook-privacy-policy-audit-checklist.pdf).

### Contacting Knowledgehook

Please contact Knowledgehook with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, our third-party disclosure practices, or your consent choices by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.knowledgehook.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)**Effective Date: May 11, 2020**

Product

Resources

Company

Get Started

Product

Resources

Company

Get Started

© 2024 Knowledgehook Inc. All rights reserved.
